Guide to the Business and Professional Women 1919-2010 bpw
Hartford Public Library, Hartford History Center, Publisher
- Inventory
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Membership Directory, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Newsletter, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 23)